it doesn't
он не
hang You don't see what it is that you
висит Не бачишь что это что вообще
don't give up your hollow at all
дупля не отдаёшь
you see what it
видишь что тея
is and
такое и
here we had a Victory Parade everything is awesome with us
вот у нас был парад Победе у нас всё
right away
офигенно сразу
Good
Добрый
afternoon
день
war is a special operation it's not
война это спецоперация это не
like that to
во ну чтоб вас
bomb you you have renounced
бомбить вы отреклись
Christ from the cross
Христа от креста
you are high from May 9  everything you can and you
высь от 9 мая вы всё что можно и вы
shout torchlight processions that Bandera is
кричите факельные шествия что Бандера -
our
это наша
tank understood And what region are you from yourself
бачка понял А вы сами с какого региона
ro from Belgorod from Belgorod By the way,
ро с Белгорода с Белгорода Кстати вам
nothing flies to you
прилетает ничего не
at all, nothing works for us
прилетает вообще у нас
at all And what about the oil ba
работает вообще А что там нефте ба
tanned
загорело
tanned How will you throw the oil ba
загорело Как там бросите нефте ба
tanned there  there was an unfortunate fire and that's
Загорела там пожар несчастный вышел да и
all and why and
всё а из-за чего а из-за
why there's no point in smoking at work and I realized
чего нечего курить на работе а я понял
This is the same guy who smoked at Kres
Это же тот самый чувак который на крес
Moscow he's now
Москва курил он сейчас у вас в Белгороде
driving somewhere in Belgorod and there he
где-то ездит Да и там
smokes glory to Russia  yes yes yes yes yes So that's it
Курит слава России да да да да да Так то
Look look don't Listen to me
Смотрите смотрите не Послушай меня
please
пожалуйста
carefully here you are  so happy you
внимательно вот ты вот такой довольный
sit
сидишь
and threw out
да выкинул
your own flag Yes, a flag is what, a camp
свой свой флаг Да флаг это что лаг
is the Republic Yes, your republic, you
это Республики Да своей республики
sit like this Probably somewhere in
вот такой сидишь Наверно где-то у
the basement
подвале
Or are you calling from Bandera from Bandera corvee
Или ты с бандер звонишь с бандер барщины
and from corvee the place is
а с барщины место
Khmelnitsky Stepan
Хмельницкий Степан
Khmelnitsky com you know Stepan x
Хмельницкий ком ты знаешь Степана х
Malinsky there Igor  show tell will
малинского вон Игоря покажи скажи
come And
приедет А вот
look Who is Stepan Khmelnitsky
смотри Кто такой Степан Хмельницкий у
you have this
вас это
hero on the shoot
герой на снима
Well you just said that nobody city
Ну ты сейчас сказал что никого город
Khmelnitsky called you
Хмельницкий называ вот вас
belgo Well
белго Ну
go That's good so you understand this is a
го Вот хорошо чтоб ты понимал это
criminal lifestyle look here is the flag of
криминальный ритет вот смотри вот флаг
theft Cool Can you
кра да Круто А можете крупным планом
show it in close-up  I looked where it hangs
показать посмотрел где он висит
where it hangs it doesn't
где он висит он не
hang You don't see what it is what do
висит Не бачишь что это что вообще
n't you give a damn about it
дупля не отдаёшь
you see what it
видишь что это
is and
такое и
here we had a Victory Parade everything is
вот у нас был парад Победе у нас всё
awesome and you thought it was all you Well I understand
Офигенно а вы рели это всё вы Ну я Поня
I
я
see you are
смотрю вы
attached Everything you are attached  I risk
прили Всё вы прили рискую
power one more question If you have not betrayed
власть ещ один вопрос Если вы не предали
Cross grandfather and so on Why do you
Креста дедо и так далее Почему вы в
live like this, everything is
таком живёте вот у вас там всё Като
broken around you there, poor
разбитое вокруг бедная
house, it's generally beautiful Well, show me the beauty ru
хата вообще красота А ну покажи красо ру
takka Don't pull,
такка Не дёргай
stop Cool and then turn about the car, the
останови Классно а дальше крути о машина
car is cool, yeah No, no, back
тачка классная да Да не не назад
Turn back further further further
Развернись назад дальше дальше дальше
More  keep spinning Well further further not here
Ещё ещё крути Ну дальше дальше не вот
behind Wow this is beauty the gates
сзади Ого вот это красота ворота
are interested forged beautiful
интересуются кованые красивые
beautiful beautiful And what can you
красивые красивые А что ты можешь
show
показать
under the basement
под подвале
Well our air defense our
Ну наши ПВО наши
javelins damn doors I wanted to say
джавелины блин двери Я хотел сказать
if
буде
our
наши
guns you will then not have your flag
орудия вы будете потом не твой флаг
hanging but the Russian Vit
висеть а российский Вить
better if  at
лучше если у
me and what
ме а как
is the name of the force the force in Truth how is
называется сила сила в Правде как село
your
ваше
village village and glory of Russia and you sit with
деревня и слава России а ты сидишь своим
your I understand that you are streaming Yes I
своём Я понимаю что ты стримишь Да
understand you perfectly and here is our flag hanging
прекрасно тебя понимаю и вот флаг висит
red red varnish hanging here and what
наш красный красный лак висит вот а что
does this
означает этот
la mean what
ла как Что
does victory mean 9  May why is it red
означает победу 9 мая почему он красный
Why is it grey And you don't recognize May 9th
Почему сер А ты что не признаёшь 9 мая
no no why is history not teaching us
не не почему вот история нас не учат
this history I want to ask you why is
этой истории Я хочу вас спросить почему
it and you don't recognize May 9th Yes  I admit
он а ты не признаёшь 9 мая Да признаю у
my grandfather fought we won f
меня дед воевал мы победили ф
this is lag red this is Victory
это лаг красный это Победы
this is the niece of all
это нение всех
republics all republics
республик всех республик
firstly secondly the flag of Victory This was
во-первых во-вторых флаг Победы Это был
chosen one flag
избран один флаг
ros And why did they make this flag
рос А почему вот это флаг сделали лагом
lag pobe name
побе имен
Lam your flag of
Лам твой флаг
Victory this is your flag of yours
Победы это твой флаг твоей
Republics of your Republic not here you have
Республики твоей Республики не вот у вас
this red flag hanging what kind of
этот красный флаг висит что это за флаг
flag is this what kind of flag is this Well the flag of Victory the flag of Victory And
это за флаг Ну флаг Победы флаг Победы А
in what year was it
в каком году его
invented invented now I will say so
придумали придумали сейчас скажу так
If I am not mistaken so numi
Если не ошибаюсь так нуми
this And do you know what the letter v is and not In
это А ты знаешь что такое буква в и не В
what  year they came up with this flag Now I
каком году придумали этот фла Сейчас я
'll tell you a
скажу
discount a
скидку
discount I'll tell you
скидку тебе скажу
so the revolution was
так революция была
917 ask what is the
917 спроси что такое
letter year was invented
буква году был придуман
fact Workers
фак Трудящихся ися
and what is the letter v and Vladimir
Ну а что такое буква в и Владимир
Zelensky I know that you are all his fans
Зеленский Я знаю что вы его фанаты все
there Vete
там Вете
book we have for
бук у нас за
powder You know
пороше Ты знаешь
Dear Sir,
Уважаемый к нам сюда Приезжают по нашей
a bunch of Ukrainian cars come to our region, we don't
области куча украинских машин мы им не
break their windows, we don't puncture
разбиваем ни стёкла мы не прокалываем
their tires, that's not how he said
шины не так он сказал
the letter and in a  what Tae e time Well, this is
буква и в а что Тае е раз Ну это ж
Vladimir Zelensky
Владимир Зеленский
[laughter]
[смех]
he is a deep person We just don't
ени глуб тый человек Мы просто не
understand Why are you
понимаем Нафига вы на военной технике
putting Vladimir Zelensky on military equipment you are
ставите Владимир Зеленский вас же
Vladimir
Владимир Вот
Look, the letter Z and in explain What is this
смотри буква Z и в объясни му Что такое
explain this for the truth for faith for faith
обясните это за правду за веру за веру
for  and for Donbass
за и за Донбасс
for you were silent for 8 years
за ж вы молчали 8 лет
when when you did not recognize it
когда когда не признали вы его
she what Putin said to the masses we will come
она что ж Путин говорил до мас придём да
and that's all if we accept the Republic This is a war for
и всё если мы Прим Республики Это война
Ukraine
Украине
poli And you are out
поли А те вых
and who are you working for Kharko wait
а кем Вот вы работаете Харько подожди
Kharkov is already in ruins one can say  is it
Харьков уже можно сказать в руинах это
good or not well for us it's
хорошо или нет ну Для нас это
bad well I'm not lying to you am I lying or not
плохо Ну я те не вру тея вру или нет
Kharkov is in ruins it's a fact you're
Харьков в руинах это факт это вы
happy
радуетесь
no and with Ostan all of Ukraine No No Yes
нет и с Остане вся Украина Нет Нет Да
go to hell then in that case all the
пошли вы тогда в таком случае всего
best t I didn't tell you a single thing
хорошего т я тебе не сказал ни одного
mata none none of
мата ни ни одного
this I am communicating with you as a
этого я с тобой общаюсь как солидарный
person of solidarity o let's as Solidarity
человек о давайте как Солидарность
Solidarity further poo Here is what you
Солидарность дальше поо Вот вы кем
do by
работаете по
profession electric welder
профессии электросварщик
electric welder That is, you have an education
электросварщик То есть у вас образование
school
школа
tamchi
тамчи
vocational school look Why
ПТУ смотри Почему
because we celebrate a day off in
потому что выходной
May
мая
from
отмечаем от
some Why
некоторых Почему
Tei there is no ribbon you understand it is here
Тей ленты нету понимаешь она здесь
inside it there is a ribbon geska
внутри него есть лента геска
ribbon inside And those
лента внутри А те
are there because because it was still under the
есть потому что потому что это ещ при
tsar And what does the tsar have to do with
царе А причём цар
Victory You ask him if there is no it is still
Победе Ты спроси у него есть нет она ещё
Under  kings walked You ask him if there is a No
При цари шла Ты спроси него есть а Нет у
I have this Knight of the Cross of St. George
меня этого кавалер георгиевского Креста
there is such a Knight of the Cross of St. George
есть такое кавалер георгиевского Креста
And do you have a heroic ribbon No I'm
А у тебя есть геройская Лента Нет яже
telling you No we have it banned at all
говорю Нет у нас она запрещена вообще
for ge And what about you there
за ге А что вас там
You can, for example, be a normal person
Можно например быть нормальным человеком
allowed to
разрешал
live
жить
normally and you
нормально а ты
bro what
братан ты кем
do you do for a living I yes I do what's the difference
работаешь Я да я работаю какая разница
No well that's interesting I'm a programmer he's an
Не ну вот интересно я программист он
electros
электрос
promi Well yes In what language and what
проми Ну да На каком языке а что
St. George ribbons are banned Yes yes they've been
Георгиевские ленты запрещены Да да у нас
banned for many years now Well what are they
запрещены уже много летно лет Ну а в чём
banned for And the fact that your grandfather fought
запрещены А то что ты твой дед воевал
this is not not
это не не
respectable But here are the St. George ribbons
чти А вот Георгиевские ленточки потому
because we have all sorts of people running around with St. George
что у нас всякие бегают с георгиевскими
ribbons there for
лентами там за
Russia
Росси
I, as a programmer, a programmer,
подм я вот как программист программиста
do you
вас сшу
think that Russia attacked
считаете Правильно ли что Россия напала
Ukraine correctly? It didn't attack. And what it
Украину она не нападала А что она
did was a military special operation
сделала это военная спецоперация потому
because Russia was forced to present it that way so that
что Россию вынудили так преподнести
it would strike so
чтобы она ударила так
that well, the
чтоб
answer is because it is wrong
ну ответ потому что это неправильно
that countries of some states
что страны некоторых государств
rule on the border with
управляют на границе с
Russia, look, in this village in the
Россией вот смотрите вы вот в этом селе
Belgorod
Белгородской
region, what's the difference to you from what
области како вам разница от того что
will happen in Ukraine, whether you need it or not, how did you live
будет в Украине надо не надо вы как жили
there, why do you need
там зачем вам
a war against us, but we don't go to you? And who goes to
война нас а мы до вас не идём А кто идт
you, no one goes to you, you just
до вас никто не идёт просто у вас
got a lot
досталось очень много
Bandera Yes and our soldiers
бандеровские Да и наших солдат
I saw a lot personally yes they
много я видел лично да
checked I saw yes And how did you see
проверяли Я видел да А как вы видели
that my
что у меня
partner's wife works in an ambulance and
у напарника работает жена на скорой и
she brought and saw this whole system
она привозила и видела эту всю систему
she saw or did you see his
она видела или вы видели его
si No she
си Нет она
saw Maybe she about Wait
видела Может она об Подожди
wait  So here
подожди Так что тут
we
мы
live
живём
in time The Russian flag must be
временем Российский флаг надо
hung And why
вешать А почему
high and because we have glory to Russia
выси а потому что у нас слава России
Glory to Putin that's how not a Russian
Слава Путину вот так не а рого
flag
флага с
I
я
hung The Russian
повесил Российский
flag
флаг
Russian
российский
Show
Покажите
me here for
вотк за
Russia for
Россию за
Russia And what are you against Russia
Россию А ты что против России
Dassia attacked my state
дассия нала на мо государство
I understand In short you Bender
я понял Короче ты Бендер
Well
Да ну
okay Russia if you say that
хорошо Россия если ты говоришь что
attacked then I will come to you and talk to
напала тогда приду до тебя и поговорят с
you and you yourself Why not come
тобой а вы сами Почему не
Prim we will come too  if Here
при е надо Прим придём и мы если Тут
in A why do we need vodka we don't need vodka
во А зачем нам водка нам водка не нужна
this
этот
iskar yes
искар
then A do you know what is the difference between point U and
да то А Вы знаете чем отличается точка У
then
то
absolutely
абсолютно
nothing at all flies and
ничего летает и
flies hammer and
летает долбят и
hammer
долб
ago We are for Vladimir Vladimirovich he he is
аго Мы за Владимира Владимировича он он
our president he is our beloved and we as
наш президент он наш любимый и нам как
if
бы
we are 55 years old
лет нам
Listen, and you voted for
55 Слышишь а ты за то что голосовал за
Zelensky, not me, you
Зеленского Да не я
see Poroshenko started
за вот видиш Порошенко развязал
a war, your Zelensky started a war, yes, and
войну Зеленский твой развязал войну Да А
you understand Ukrainian Ukrainian
вы разбираетесь в Украинской Украинской
politics, and you are for Ukraine, yes, look, you understand
политике Да и ты за Украину Да смотрите
your Russian politics,
в своей политике российской вы
I understand, and who  you have a head
я разбираюсь А кто у вас глава
chairman of the State
председатель это Государственной
Duma who Matveenko is not chairman of
Думы кого Матвеенко нет председатель
the state A yes I am not very political
государственно А да я политику сильно не
That is, you tell us what we
То есть вы вот нам рассказываете что нам
need to do And you in your politics
надо делать А вы в своей политике не
you don't understand
разбираетесь
at all they will free you from Bandera and everything will be
вообще от бандеро освободят и будет всё
Russian to me in general something there
российское мне вообще чтото там мне
tells me in general why did you
рассказывает вообще зачем вам вы были
ever go to Europe no it I don't need
когда-то в Европе не она мне не нужна
Europe And in general I don't need anything I
Европа И вообще мне ничего не нужно мне
just want peace on my head and that's all I don't give
лишь бы мир был на головой и всё мне
a damn who
еро кто
attacked why did you start
напал зачем вы начали
a special operation to protect Donbass wait
спецоперацию по защите Донбасса подожди
under protection Donbass to protect from
под защитой Донбасс чтоб защитить от
these hips who you
этих бедеров которые ты с кем
are talking to if they attacked Russia
разговариваешь если б напали на Россию
Well so what if a woman
Ну ну и что пусть женщина
no woman does not fit oh I understand everything
нет женщина не влазит ой всё я понял
Sorry that
Извините что
I glory to Russia look at the lady who is
я слава России смотрите госпожа которая
there  I will apologize to you behind the scenes
там за кадром принесу вам свои извинения
I realized that I can't joke with you
Я понял что с вами шутить нельзя
this is some
это ваша какая-то
acquaintance of yours Yes yes this is an acquaintance And this is Igoryan
знакомая Да да это знакомая А это Игорян
sitting Igoryan
сидит Игорян
Show me where o a Well, I
Покажи вот где о а Ну поближе Игоря
can
можно
take a closer look at Igor And like this right now Well let's go
посмотрю А вот так сечас Ну давай я
Ira and how Yes just  bring it closer
иря а как Да просто поднеси ближе е
Here is Igoryan sitting where
Вот вот Игорян сидит где
Igoryan Well, don't lower it lower about Igoryan
Игорян А ну ниже нез опустите о Игорян
military IRN glory to
военный ирн слава
Russia glory to Russia
России слава России
yes brother you  who because of whom I am for
да братишка ты кто из-за кого я за
Zelensky here we have already come to the
Зеленского тут мы пришли уже в
Belgorod
Белгородскую
region for Zelensky yes
область за Зеленского да
yes here Poroshenko and ye Battalions were sent to
да тут Порошенко ие Батальоны послали
you in the Belgorod region of Ukraine yes oh
вам в Белгородскую область Украине да о
yes to the heroes
да героям
Glory don't wait Igoryan a Well get up
Слава не подожди Игорян а Ну встань
Try to get up
Попробуй встать
Igoryan Try to get up I would get up you
Игорян Попробуй встать я вста был бы ты
you would be here next to me I stood up Show
ты был бы ты здесь рядом я встал Покажи
Russia stand on your knees why did you sit down in front of a Ukrainian like that
Россия стот с колен что ж ты так перед
Tanka proud Russian
сел Танька гордый русский
[ __ ] I can't see him well chu correcting the camera Oh
руй я его Плохо вижу чу поправ камеру О
yes I see that and I need to lower it a little bit
да я вижу так и надо чуть-чуть вниз
oh come here you I'll break it so
опустить о приедь сюда тея разобью так
good  And where Where to come What village
хорошо А где Куда приехать Какое село
What
Какое
village Come And Igor got
село Приезжай А Испугался Игор
scared Yes, you got scared you won't even get up
Да испугался ты же даже не встанешь
now right now you won't be able to
сейчас вот сейчас вот ты не сможешь
get up you can get up And are you sure sure a Well get
встать сможешь встать А ты уверен уверен
up how will you I'll get up a well come on well
а Ну встань как ты я встану а ну давай
come on do
ну давай
n't get up not a
не встане неста
Irva horse  Of course the Russians will rise
Ирва коне встане конечно да русские на
knee Russian on Kolya not Russian not on
колене русски на Коле не русские не на
knees It's you on your knees not me who sat down you
коленях Это ты на коленях не я сел
will soon soon you will be on your knees
будешь скоро скоро будешь ты на коленях
Well look You don't sew on your knees you are a
Ну смотри Ты же не шь на коленях ты
normal person He on
нормальный человек Он на
Kolya in Russian you will be on your knees give
Коле по-русски будешь на колени верните
me back Igoryan I am with
мне игоряна я с
him I am  I'll tell you that glory to Russia and
ним я тебе скажу что слава России и
Vladimir Vladimirovich is our president
Владимир Владимирович это наш президент
and he is our end the conversation I'll tell you
и он наш заканчивай разговор я те ещё
again our beloved that you are a woman
раз наш любимый то что ты вот женщина
commanding you a woman is my wife she
командует женщина это моя жена она
commands
командует
me she doesn't command she is the main one for what you are
ми не командует она главная за то что ты
yes for what you are
да за то что ты
and  oh Igoryan stood up
и о Игорян встал
respect apology further camera move away
извинение дальше камеру отодвинь
head Come on move away
голо Давай отодвинул
you Well and you SOBR with your head or not
ты Ну а вы СОБРа головой своей или нет
Who are you
Ты кто
and the phone Teo look normally In the
и телефон Тео посмотри нормально В
phone video calls
телефо те видеосвязи
you know different types not this who This
вы знаете разго типа не это кто Это
listen this is a representative of the Ukrainian special
слышь это представитель украинских спец
services
спецслужб
You are a fool what are you  you're digging a completely
сь Ты дура что ты роешь вообще
abnormal person who are you I'm just doing a
ненормальный Ты кто Я просто делаю
program called ZMI animals right
передачу ЗМИ животных называется вот
now Igoryan I'm watching and can you tell me
сейчас Игорян смотрю а можно
the program is over everything in the world animals
те передача закончилась всё в мире живот
Let's
Давайте
eat
сть
propane g let him sleep it off he will
пропана г пусть он проспится он
sleep it off here
проспится вот
came a Russian woman who will
пришла русская женщина которая там избу
enter the hot hut with a horse on with some six There
горячую войдёт коня на с како шесть Там
and that's all the guys the broadcast was interrupted now
и всё пацанам эфир перервала зараз
in short Igor will be a popandos Zhenka will be a
короче Игоря буде попандос Женьку буда
popandos the third grove where did he
попандос третий рощ куда с
disappear That's all of Russia and a
пропал Вот и вся Россия да
mess But the Victory Banner in short
бардак Зато Знамя Победы Короче
so write to y Telegram right now axis VN
так пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show to people at times I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams that for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
you we Mali active links write
тоб ми Мали активный звязок пишиться
right now and Popik there  in telegrams
прямо зараз а Попик там в телеграми
okrim video tezh tsikava and useful
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are obliged to you
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
trimati constant operational links
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Slava  ukrainian write
YouTube Слава украини пиши
with
с